filesaveas.com 2011-01-17

# FileSaveAs Website Privacy Policy

## Our Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy, and do not give or sell any information that you may provide us with to third parties.

By using this website, you agree to accept our Privacy Policy. Be aware that our Privacy Policy may be subject to change. Changes to our Privacy Policy will appear on this web page. 

### Information gathered from visitors

In common with other websites, log files are stored on the web server saving details such as the visitor's IP address, browser type, referring page and time of visit.

Visitors that wish to interact with site's discussion forum will be required to register. Registering results in the visitor's email address, a username and password will be stored on the web server. Additional information can be entered optionally by the user to form of a user profile.

An email newsletter service is offered by this site. Should a visitor elect to join the mailing list, their email address, plus email preferences, will be stored on the server.

Cookies may be used to remember visitor preferences when interacting with the website.

### How the Information is used

Visitor information as outlined on this page is used to monitor and improve the performance of our websites and services, and enhance the visitor's experience when using the website.

Where a visitor opts in to our email mailing list or registers with our discussion forum, the email address may be used to provide visitors with emails relating to our services, as well as news updates and additional information.

Email addresses will not be sold, rented or leased to third parties.

If requested, we may submit your information to local or government authorities. 

### Visitor Options

If you have subscribed to one of our services, you may unsubscribe by following the instructions which are included in email that you receive.

You may be able to block cookies via your browser settings but this may prevent you from accessing certain features of the website, such as some forum functionality.

### Content submitted to this site

To offer a better service to site visitors, we may republish extracts of emails sent to this website, comments made in our discussion forum, comments made to blog posts, or other messages sent to us electronically. Should we elect to republish content, we will not disclose any user's email address, telephone number or postal address. 

If you do not want us to republish any extracts from content or correspondence submitted to us, then then this should be made clear in the body text at the time of submission.

### Cookies

Cookies are small digital signature files that are stored by your web browser that allow your preferences to be recorded when visiting the website. They may be used to track your return visits to the website.

Operating costs for running this website are funded by site advertising using affiliate networks. Some advertisement placements on this website make use of third-party cookies from one or more advertising networks. These cookies use anonymous data to improve the advertising experience for visitors, for tracking purposes, and to attribute advertising impressions to this website.

You may be able to block cookies via your browser settings but this may prevent you from accessing certain features of the website, such as some forum functionality.

### Google Advertising

This site displays advertising using the Google advertising network. Third-party vendors including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a visitor's prior visits to websites that use the network. 

Website visitors may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

* * *

Should you have any queries regarding this website's Privacy Policy, please contact us using our Contact Us page.
